bemybb.com 2015-03-15

# BeMyBB | Privacy

**BeMyBB Privacy Policy**

Last Updated on December 11, 2013

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of this website, BeMyBB.com (the "Site", "we" or "us").

**California Residents**

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: (a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name and email address, the URL for the website you visited, and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Please e-mail your request to legal@bemybb.com.

**Information We May Collect From You**

During sign up, and at other times during your use of the Site, we may require that you provide us with certain information, which could include "Account Data" (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, and password), "Financial Data" (i.e., credit card/billing information) along with "Demographic Information." Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history.

**How is this Information Used?**

Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors as necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.

We may use "cookies" and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Site according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in.

We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Site.

Account Data will be shared as determined by you through the controls in your account.

**Profile Data**

Your user profile will display the information that you choose to share about yourself with other users of the Site. You may have the option to hide some of the information on your user profile from public view, for example your marital status and your date of birth.

Your public user profile may contain a list your activities on the Site.

We may also display information about your activities throughout the Site in the user profile pages of the user(s) who are on your friends list. If you choose to post photos or other images on your user profile, these may also be displayed on your user profile and may be seen by other users of the Site.

On your user profile pages you may add, delete and make changes to your user profile information, which may be seen by other users of the Site.

We reserve the right to disable your user account if we find, in our sole opinion, that your account has submitted or uploaded inappropriate content, including, but not limited to, content in violation of our [Terms of Use](http://bemybb.com/terms/).

**Financial Data**

Credit card transactions are processed via industry standard encryption through third party processors, which processors only use your information for that purpose. Financial Data is considered private information and will not be shared with us or with third parties except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding by you that such transaction(s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party.

**You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third Parties**

Financial Data or other data provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on the Site or in response to emails sent to you by the Site are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party's terms and conditions and privacy policy.

**Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety**

Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system. We also may share all of your information in order to protect the rights or property of BeMyBB or our users, or third parties.

**Emails From Us and Use of Your Email Address**

Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to the Site. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us please unsubscribe by updating your notifications on [your email preferences page](http://bemybb.com/profiles/account/) or send us an email to [cancel@bemybb.com](mailto:cancel@bemybb.com). You may also receive emails from us related to our service or, in connection with your profile on the Site. We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, which purport to promote the Site.

**Advertisements**

We may utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to measure advertising effectiveness on an "anonymous" basis. Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Site. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to fulfill your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Site on such advertisers' website(s).

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this privacy policy at any time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.

**Changes in the Ownership of the Site**

The Site is a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Financial Data and Account Data) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website, by email at [support@bemybb.com](mailto:support@bemybb.com).
